We'll be right back.
The Straw Hat Pirates are the culprits?
The protectors of the City of Water!
Luffy, let me talk to Ice Pops.
This has to be a mistake.
There's no way it was Robin.
We'd be fools to let you anywhere near him.
Criminals have no right to make demands.
He's right!
Tie up the culprits!
Those bastards can't get away with shooting our hero!
Send him to the gallows!
Hey, wait!
Just calm down!
Hold on!
What?
You can't fool me, Missy.
I saw you with that Straw Hat guy.
I bet you're one of the criminals, aren't you?
Really?
Yeah, she was riding along with him on a Yagra when he got here.
We've got you now.
You're gonna get what you deserve.
Stop it!
Let me go!
Nami!
I'm telling you people, we didn't do anything wrong!
You're making a mistake!
It wasn't if we trust anything you say!
You scumbags are pirates and probably assassins, too!
This doesn't even make any sense!
There's no reason why Robin would attack him!
Yeah!
Not only that, we'd never even heard of Iceberg until we met him yesterday!
You brats just keep saying that all you want.
It's over.
Fact is, you picked on the wrong guy.
The moral of the story is, if you make an enemy out of Iceberg,
then you make an enemy out of the entire Galilag Company.
And that's not the half of it.
You also made an enemy out of everyone in this whole city.
You understand?
Listen, I don't want to fight any of you!
We can still talk about all this, okay?
I don't give a damn what you want!
Word of this is going to spread like wildfire.
There's no place to run and no place to hide.
It's the end of the road.
You pirates are going down.
That's what you get for messing with Galilag!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?
You're not even going to go out with a fight?
I just told you!
We're not enemies and I don't want to fight any of you!
Since pistols don't work on you, we'll have to go with plan B.
Damn it all!
I guess these guys are going all out, huh?
No, he got away.
Well, they almost had me.
And we're going on, huh?
I can't dodge anymore.
Yeah!
That's right!
All right!
Nice shot!
Yeah!
And that's why galley laws are pride and joy!
Woo!
Feels good to see them lose!
You bet!
I hope they blow that sorry sucker sky high!
Ooh!
Nah, I shouldn't say that.
After all, Straw Hat's our enemy too.
And I haven't beaten him nearly enough.
Not yet.
And to be fair, I was here first.
Wasn't I?
I enjoyed your little show,
but this is my stage,
and the only star here is Frankie.
So get out of my way!
Kelly Law!
Hold your horses.
We'll be done with them in a second,
then you can fight us to your heart's content.
Listen, you.
I called dibs on Straw Hat before all of you even got here.
Screw it.
You don't even care what I say, do you?
Pauly, watch out!
Get out of there!
Frankie's going nuts again!
Run away!
Huh?
Connector set.
He brought down a crane with that attack.
It's lethal!
That was him?
Looks like a cannon hit it.
He's about to fire!
Get him broke!
Your cannon's ready to go!
Hey!
Don't expect me to shoot a cannonball or anything.
The shells I fire are made of nothing but air.
Still, these babies break the speed of sound.
Air, huh?
Run for your lives!
Light!
What the hell?!
...
Tu defaas!
Ah!
Man, he was a kitten. That thing hits like a hurricane to the face.
Another brain is coming down!
Get out of here! It's gonna bustle on us!
Hurry up!
Here it comes!
Yeah, let it fall!
Hell, I don't care.
Let's bring the whole damn shipyard down!
He really is a cyborg.
I thought he was kidding, but that air shot was no joke.
I've never even seen technology like that.
But hey.
No more angry mob at least.
Nami! Run!
Luffy! You didn't get hit back there, did you?
It's gonna take a lot more than that if those guys wanna get rid of me.
Okay, come on. We gotta get going.
I'm not sure how, but we gotta talk to Ice Pops.
What? Now?
When the whole town is out searching for us?
Hey, look! Straw Hat's getting away!
Uh-oh.
They're trying to surround us.
Nami!
Huh?
Here, hold on tight, okay?
No, not okay!
Stop them!
They're too fast!
Follow them!
And we're too fast!
jobs!
What?
Well, he's not on the deck at least.
Maybe he's still too hurt to move.
But if we don't want him to recognize us, we can't risk getting any closer.
Here we go. You ready to do this?
What's that? There's a gigantic storm called Aqua Laguna that's on its way here right now?
That's right! By midnight tonight, this entire beach will be completely underwater as well as half of the town! Crazy, huh?
That's terrible! We should get out of here right away!
Yes, sir! If we were smart, that's exactly what we would do!
Let's evacuate to higher ground!
That's a good idea! Let's do that!
Evacuate!
That's weird.
I could have sworn I heard someone out here.
Be sure to evacuate!
Evacuate, Isabel!
They were saying something about a storm.
Well, actually, the wind is awfully strong, isn't it?
Bro?
They're getting away. Don't you want to go after them?
Nah, that last coup de vin did ate up all my fuel.
See this? My pompadour's limp.
No kidding. It looks like a willow swaying in the wind.
What a mess, stupid Galilwa.
But I'll take care of that straw hat as soon as I'm done refueling.
That kid ain't half bad, you know?
He certainly earned his big bounty.
Jeez Louise.
Even for Frankie, this is too much.
Today just isn't our day.
Frankie or no Frankie, we can't let straw hat escape.
Aqua Laguna is gonna hit tonight.
There are only two sea train departures left today.
Since the straw hats can't leave on their ship,
the sea train's the only ticket they've got to get off the island.
This is our chance.
Have every member of Galilwa spread out and hunt them down.
We'll settle this before sunset.
Granny, look! It's water seven!
Don't get too excited and fall in the ocean now!
If that isn't Galilwa HQ, I don't know what is.
No surprise, since it's right next to Dock 1.
And look!
The place is totally swarming with reporters.
Those tough-looking guys are probably shipwrights.
It takes us to write, will they still learn?
And this team's story.
And if they are all ready to...
Lee St recommend during...
And they love this series I'd have been going to watch for the abundantly!
Ready?
Where we go next?
The week in Ohio...
2nd November.
This week I will never finish line.
The personal life...
It's great for everyone.
When you pass to cliffh FR***
oys in the ocean...
疲れ果てた向きの中でも変わらないもの探すコンバスで いつまでも持っていれるから
いつか辿り着く夢の終わりに できるだけこのままで大人に 見上げた果てしないこの大空に 永遠に 永遠に
幼き頃の夢物語 忘られち記憶の糸たどり 未だ胸を焦がす残り火を消してしまわないように
乱れた晴れ渡るこの空に 仲間と共に想いを託し 移り変わる時代を越え 永遠に 永遠に
доザ実に当たる出折れしー motherで 皆に永遠に alotを見るのだろう
горびん感梨その日トミーは 永遠に中東変わり リンゴも見られるまで 永遠にそれでは
ゴムサヒ feminine 恋かしく思いがして 永遠が示いべき 誰につきなら
I'm gonna be king of the park!